Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory02 Mss.B.B61.inventory02
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents B
  - Burrows, Elizabeth S. (Box 12)
    - To Paul W. Gordon, 1933 Sep. 2; 2p
      - attached to letter from PWG to FB, 1933 Sep. 30
  - Burschenschaft Alemannia zu Bonn (Box 12)
    - invitation, 1910 July 29
    - program, 1911 July 29
    - statement, 1935 May 16; 1p
  - Burschen Verein Alter (Box 12)
    - 1919 Sep. 12, 1p
  - Burstein, Abraham (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 6; 1p
  - Burt, M.W. (Mrs. W.C.) (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1924
    - From Boas, 1924 June 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 June 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 July 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 May 15; 1p
  - Burton, Ernest D. (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1920 July 24; 3p
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 July 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 23; 1p
  - Burton, Marion Lerey (Box 12)
    - From James Thayer Gerould, 1923 Jan. 29; 2p
  - Burtt, E.A. (Box 12)
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 7; 1p
    - EAB -- to H. Gaston-Heye, 1940 Dec.
  - Busch, Julius (Box 12)
    - To Boas, 1885 Mar. 22
    - To Boas, 1886 Jan. 26
  - Buschan, Georg (Box 12)
    - To Boas, 1895 Sep. 22; 3p
    - To Boas, 1899 Apr. 27
  - Bush, A.S. -- (House of Rep.) (Box 12)
    - To Boas, 1894 Dec. 20
  - Bush, W.T. (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1926 July 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 June 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 21
    - To Boas, 1926 July 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 June 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 3; 3p
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 31; 2p
    - BV -- from K.T. Compton, 1933 May 31
  - Bushee, Frederick A. (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1925 May 12; 2p
    - see FB open letter, Spain, 1938 Jan.
  - Buske, Hans - Verlagsbuchhandlung (Box 12)
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 15; 1p
  - Busse, A. (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 13; 1p
      - copies to v. Klenze
      - C. Kayser
      - J. Speyer
      - K. Frank
      - E. Baruch, etc.
    - see FB to C. V. Klenze, 1920 Nov. 24
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 1
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 11
    - From Boas, 1936 June 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jul. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Sep. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 31; 1p
    - see Emergency Sec... Art, 1920 Dec. 31
  - Busse, Gisela von (Box 12)
    - To Boas, 1931 May 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 2; 3p
      - enc. C. Klenze to F. Schmidt-Ott, 1931 Aug. 18
  - Bussman (Box 12)
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 9; 3p
  - Butcher, B.N. (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1915 June 24
    - To Boas, 1915 July 30
  - Butler, E.S. (Box 12)
    - To Boas, 1918 May 2; 1p
  - Butler, Nicholas Murray (Box 12-13)
    - From Boas - report, 1901 Oct. 21; 17p
    - From Boas, 1902 Apr. 7; 7p
    - From Boas, 1902 Apr. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1902 June 18; 4p
    - From Boas Report, 1902 Nov. 15; 10 p
    - From Boas, 1903 Feb. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1903 Mar. 5; 3p
    - From Boas, 1903 Aug. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 Aug. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 Aug. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 Sep. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 Oct. 12 & Nov. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 8; 4p
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 11; 7p
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 19; 5p
    - From Boas, 1904 Mar. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1904 Mar. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Mar. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Mar. 7; 12 p
    - From Boas, 1904 Apr. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 May 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1904 Sep. 18
    - From Boas, 1904 Nov. 9; 9p
    - From Boas, 1904 Oct. 13; 4p
    - From Boas, 1905 Jan. 3
    - From Boas, 1905 Feb. 25
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 23
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 25
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 27
    - From Boas, 1905 May 11
    - From Boas, 1905 May 25
    - From Boas, 1905 June 1
    - From Boas, 1905 June 13
    - From Boas, 1905 June 15
    - From Boas, 1905 July 3
    - From Boas, 1905 Aug. 2
    - From Boas, 1905 Aug. 12
    - From Boas, 1905 Sep. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 Sep. 27
    - From Boas, 1905 Sep. 28
    - enc. with FB to Laura Gill, 1905 Sep. 29
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 3
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 15
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 8
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 5
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 27
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 10
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 14
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 23
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 28
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 5
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 30
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 5
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 5
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 12
    - From Boas, 1906 May 12
    - From Boas, 1906 May 22
    - From Boas, 1906 May 25
    - From Boas, 1906 July 2
    - From Boas, 1906 July 14
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 12
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 30
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 30
    - From Boas, 1906 Nov. 14
    - From Boas, 1906 Nov. 16
    - From Boas, 1906 Nov. 30
    - From Boas, 1906 Dec. 5
    - From Boas, 1906 Dec. 10
    - From Boas, 1906 Dec. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Dec. 18
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 14
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 9
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 9; 19p
      - 1908 correspondence, 1908 Nov. 10; 1p
      - follows 1909 herein, 1909 Jan. 16
    - From Boas, 1909 Jan. 19
    - From Boas, 1909 Jan. 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 Jan. 23
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 3
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 5
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 13
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 16
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 19
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 25
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 26
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 2
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 12
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 May 23
    - From Boas, 1909 June 14; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1909 June 14
    - From Boas, 1909 June 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 July 3
    - From Boas, 1909 July 8
    - From Boas, 1909 Sep. 25
    - From Boas, 1909 Sep. 25
    - From Boas, 1909 Sep. 28
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 9
    - From Boas, 1909 Nov. 10
    - From Boas, 1909 Nov. 13; 6p
    - From Boas, 1909 Nov. 16
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 18
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 22
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 2; 5p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 5
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 26
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1908 May 19
    - From Boas, 1908 May 25
    - From Boas, 1908 June 23
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 1
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 22; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 13; 6p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 20
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 28; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 5
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 21
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 31
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 4
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 4
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 15
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 18
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 19
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 19
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 8; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 14
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 16
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 30; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 11
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 12
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 25
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 26
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 26
    - From Boas, 1910 May 7
    - From Boas, 1910 May 26; 3p
    - From Boas, 1910 May 27; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 May 27
    - From Boas, 1910 June 1
    - From Boas, 1910 June 4
    - From Boas, 1910 June 4
    - From Boas, 1910 June 29
    - From Boas, 1910 July 1
    - From Boas, 1910 Sep. 30
    - From Boas, 1910 Oct. 28; 9p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 14
    - From Boas, 1910 Dec. 4; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Dec. 31 & Dec. 27
    - From Boas, 1910 Dec. 28; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 4
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 6; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 27
    - From Boas, 1911 Feb. 7; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Feb. 7; 5p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 29; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 3
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 6; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 6
    - From Boas, 1911 May 11
    - From Boas, 1911 May 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Nov. 6; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1912 Apr. 10
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 3
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 3
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 23
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 27
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 4
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 16
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 27
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 14; 3p.
    - see FB to E. Seler also, 1913 Feb. 21
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 24
    - From Boas, 1913 Apr. 2
    - From Boas, 1913 Apr. 8
    - From Boas, 1913 May 19
    - see FB to E.A. Chavez also, 1913 Aug. 10
    - From Boas, 1913 Sep. 26; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Sep. 28; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 7
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 7; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 10
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 11
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 14; 15 p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 8
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 10
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 15
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 16; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 20; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 24
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 7; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 11; 4p
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 20
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 3
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 6
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 18
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 27
    - From Boas, 1914 May 18
    - From Boas, 1914 Sep. 24
    - From Boas, 1914 Sep. 24
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 29
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 14; 4p
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 2
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Mar. 2
    - From Boas, 1915 Mar. 27; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 5
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 14
    - From Boas, 1915 May 12
    - From Boas, 1915 May 25
    - From Boas, 1915 May 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 May 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 23
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 26
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 29; 5p
    - From Boas, 1915 Dec. 17; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Dec. 21
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 14; 3p
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 14; 3p
    - From Boas, 1916 Mar. 23
    - From Boas, 1916 Mar. 27
    - From Boas, 1916 May 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 May 22
    - From Boas, 1916 May 22
    - From Boas, 1916 June 2; 3p
    - From Boas, 1916 June 2; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 24
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 27
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 2; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 18; 9p
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 25; 12p
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 15
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 29; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 9
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 10
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 23; 3p
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 23
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 6
    - From Boas, 1917 Sep. 29; 4p
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 26
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 2; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 12; 4p
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 30; 1p
    - sent to Dean Woodridge lon May 24, 1918, 1918 May 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 May 3; 3p
    - From Boas, 1918 May 4; 3p
    - From Boas, 1918 May 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 June 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 June 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 July 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Jan. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Jan. 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 1; 3p
    - attached Fackenthal to FB, 1919 May 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 13; 4p
    - From Boas, 1921 Jan. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 30; 4p
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1922 Oct. 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 25; 2p
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1922 Dec. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 May 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 May 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 May 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Dec. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Dec. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Jan. 5; 2p
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 31, Mar. 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1926 Dec. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 19; 1p
    - enc. Dept. Anthrop. 11p, 1927 Feb. 26; 4p
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 May 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 5; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 1; 4p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Feb. 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1928 Feb. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Feb. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 May 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 July 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 July 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 28; 4p
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Feb. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Mar. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 May 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 May 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 May 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 31; 1p
    - cc to John Dewey and Edward B. Wilson, 1939 Jan. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 4; 6p
    - From Boas, 1941 Jan. 2; 6p
    - To Boas, 1891 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1891 Dec. 18
    - To Boas, 1903 Apr. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Apr. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Sep. 12
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 24; 3p
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 25; ko
    - To Boas, 1904 Jan. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 May 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 14
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 27
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 3
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 1
    - To Boas, 1905 May 1
    - To Boas, 1905 May 1
    - To Boas, 1905 May 12
    - To Boas, 1905 June 2
    - To Boas, 1905 June 19
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 9
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 26
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 19
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 20
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 31
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 6
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 12
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 15
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 26
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 28
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 9
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 31
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 2
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 9
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 14
    - To Boas, 1906 May 7
    - To Boas, 1906 May 22
    - To Boas, 1906 May 25
    - To Boas, 1906 May 28
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 25
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 15
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 2
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 4
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 4
    - To Boas, 1907 May 13
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 17
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 7
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 9
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 23
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 27
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 30
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 5
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 19
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 21
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 25
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 26
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 15
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 15
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 18
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 18
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 25
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 2
    - To Boas, 1909 May 3
    - To Boas, 1909 May 29
    - To Boas, 1909 June 18
    - To Boas, 1909 Sep. 24
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 8
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 12
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 Nov. 18
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 24
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 17
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 21
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 10
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 10
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 28
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 4
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 4
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1910 May 31
    - To Boas, 1910 June 4
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 22
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 4
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 5
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 16
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 25
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 7
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 16
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 30
    - To Boas, 1911 Apr. 7
    - To Boas, 1911 May 11
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 21
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 4
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 23
    - To Boas, 1912 June 3
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 15
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 27
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 7
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 17
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 3
    - To Boas, 1913 Apr. 3
    - To Boas, 1913 Apr. 7
    - To Boas, 1913 July 15
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 29
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 9
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 16
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 17
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 21
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 9
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 10
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 10
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 12
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 2
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 20
    - To Boas, 1914 Sep. 23
    - To Boas, 1914 Sep. 26
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 23
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 28
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 3
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 1
    - To Boas, 1915 June 8
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 20
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 2
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 10
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 24
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 26
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 16; 3p
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 25
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 25
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 25
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 2
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 2
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 8
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 12
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 5
    - To Boas, 1917 June 13
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 24
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 27
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 June 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 June 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 July 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 May 20; 1p
      - enc. NMB to G.G. Heye, 1927 May 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 July 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 July 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Sep. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 June 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Feb. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Sep. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 May 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Jan. 6; 3p
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 30; 1p
    - To Adler, Felix, 1908 Jan. 6
    - To Benedict, R.F., 1940 Oct. 8; 2p
    - To E.P. Boas, 1942 Dec. 21; 1p
    - To Brodrick, A.H., 1933 July 5; 1p
    - To Brodrick, A.H., 1933 July 21; 1p
    - To Dunning, W.A., 1917 Feb. 13
    - To Ferrand, L., 1912 Jan. 8
    - To Hays, W.H., 1933 Feb. 25; 1p
    - To Hays, W.H., 1933 Mar. 6; 1p
    - To Heye, G.G., 1916 Dec. 22; 2p
    - To Heye, G.G., 1920 May 20; 1p
      - (enc. with NMB, 1927 May 20)
    - To McAvoy, Clifford T., 1938 Jan. 7; 1p
      - (enc. with CTM to Efron, D., 1938 Jan. 31)
    - To Seligman, 1917 May 12; 2p
    - From Abbott, Arletta, 1906 Feb. 14
    - From Anon, 1915 June 30
    - From Brodrick, A.H., 1933 July 11
      - (enc. with NMB to AHB, 1933 July 5
    - From Burnham, A.A., 1906 Mar. 14
    - From Collier, J., 1936 Dec. 31
    - From DC!valos, Balbino, 1906 July 2
    - From Day, E.E., 1932 Apr. 7
    - From Day, E.E., 1933 Mar. 1
    - From Dunne, M. Walter, 1906 Mar.; 1p
    - From Fansler, D.S., 1931 Jan. 17
    - From Fansler, D.S., 1931 Feb. 8
    - From Fansler, D.S., 1931 Dec. 22
    - From Goddard, P.E., 1915 July 15
    - From Joyce, T.A., 1933 June 2
    - From Kronenberg, M. von, 1935 July 9
    - From Lane, F.K., 1916 Dec. 11
    - From Lester, R.M., 1939 Apr. 10
    - From Marcus, B.K., 1928 July 17
    - From Mexico, Embassy, 1906 July 2
    - From Reid, W.A., 1905 June 20
    - From Robinson, C., 1912 Jan. 25
    - From Routhewstrauch, Walter, 1938 Mar. 3
    - From Shapiro, I.F., 1931 Sep. 25
    - From Skiff, F.D., 1907 Sep. 26
    - From Taft, W.H., 1905 Apr. 26
    - From Thorndike, A.H., 1919 Oct. 30
    - From Thompson, N.S., 1933 Mar. 17
      - (enc. with Hayden, P., 1933 Mar. 21)
    - From Thompson, N.S., 1934 Apr. 25
    - From Woodbridge, F.J.E., 1918 May 10; 1p
  - Butler, Wm. T. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 8; 3p
  - Buttenwieser, B.J. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 4; 1p
  - Buttolph, Mrs. Frank E. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 30; 3p
  - Buturlin, S.A. (Box 14)
    - To Nansen, F., 1927 May 3; 2p
    - To Nansen, F., 1926 Nov. 9; 7p
    - To Nansen, F., 1927 Jan. 24
  - Buxton, N.G. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1900 July 23; 6p
  - Buyssens, Paul (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 16; 1p
  - Bye, G.T. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 24; 1p
  - Byrnes, P.R. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1931 Sep. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 20; 1p